Guide to the John Gerassi Oral History Collection ALBA.AUDIO.018
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Oral History Interviews., 62364
  - Watt, George, 1980; cuid9241; 62391 (Item ALBA A 18-201, Box 2, Cd ALBA A 18-201 A-B)
  - Watt, George, 1980; cuid9242; 62390 (Item ALBA A 18-202, Box 1, Cd ALBA A 18-202 A-B)
  - Watt, George, 1980; cuid9243; 62389 (Item ALBA A 18-203, Box 2, Cd ALBA A 18-203 A-B)
  - Watt, George, 1980; cuid9244; 62388 (Item ALBA A 18-204, Box 2, Cd ALBA A 18-204 A-B)
  - Waywood, Wally, 1980; cuid9245; 62387 (Item ALBA A 18-205, Box 2, Cd ALBA A 18-205 A-B)
  - Weissman, Irving, 1980; cuid9246; 62386 (Item ALBA A 18-206)
  - Weissman, Irving, 1980; cuid9247; 62385 (Item ALBA A 18-207)
  - Weissman, Irving, 1980; cuid9248; 62384 (Item ALBA A 18-208)
  - Weissman, Irving, 1980; cuid9249; 62383 (Item ALBA A 18-209)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9250; 62382 (Item ALBA A 18-210)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9251; 62381 (Item ALBA A 18-211)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9252; 62380 (Item ALBA A 18-212)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9253; 62379 (Item ALBA A 18-213)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9254; 62378 (Item ALBA A 18-214)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9255; 62377 (Item ALBA A 18-215)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9256; 62376 (Item ALBA A 18-216)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9257; 62375 (Item ALBA A 18-217)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9258; 62374 (Item ALBA A 18-218)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9259; 62373 (Item ALBA A 18-219)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9260; 62372 (Item ALBA A 18-220)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9261; 62371 (Item ALBA A 18-221)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9262; 62370 (Item ALBA A 18-222)
  - Zawadowski, Joe, 1980; cuid9263; 62369 (Item ALBA A 18-223)
  - Veterans' Anniversary Event: African American Veterans Honored., Undated; cuid9264; 62368 (Item ALBA A 18-224)
  - Veterans' Research Notes: Cleveland University, Undated; cuid9265; 62367 (Item ALBA A 18-225)
  - Veterans'Research Notes: Toronto Public Library, Undated; cuid9266; 62366 (Item ALBA A 18-226)
  - Villis, Ray: Contract with Gerassi, Undated; cuid9267; 62365 (Item ALBA A 18-227)